<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Raghava Uppuluri on Purdue ARC</title><link>https://purduearc.com/authors/raghava-uppuluri/</link><description>Recent content in Raghava Uppuluri on Purdue ARC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://purduearc.com/authors/raghava-uppuluri/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://purduearc.com/post/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://purduearc.com/post/about/</guid><description>The Autonomous Robotics Club of Purdue was created to grow the skills and abilities of its members through design projects centered around advanced autonomous robotics systems. It provides hands-on, real world experience to interdisciplinary teams using industry standard tools and practices.
Through ARC, members can meet like-minded individuals, solve real world robotics problems, gain experience with industry-standard tools, and build their career portfolios. We welcome new members of any skill level and provide an environment for members to learn about topics such as state estimation, control algorithms, and machine learning.</description></item><item><title>Robot Arm Project Fall 2021</title><link>https://purduearc.com/post/f21-robot-arm-announcement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://purduearc.com/post/f21-robot-arm-announcement/</guid><description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Raghava, the Robot Arm project software lead, this fall along with Sara who is our hardware lead.
If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re interested in being apart of the robot arm project! I&amp;rsquo;m excited to work with you guys and build an awesome robot arm.
Onboarding So, I&amp;rsquo;m a new project member, what should I do?
So, if you&amp;rsquo;re new to the project, we&amp;rsquo;ll try our best to get you up to speed ASAP on our project with our onboarding tools we built:</description></item></channel></rss>