<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Purdue ARC</title><link>https://www.purduearc.com/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Purdue ARC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.purduearc.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall 2021 Callout (Round 2)</title><link>https://www.purduearc.com/post/f21-new-project-callout/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.purduearc.com/post/f21-new-project-callout/</guid><description>ARC will be hosting another round of callouts in response to two new projects that were pitched for the semester.
If you are interested in working with human-hand animatronics or autonomous UAVs, then be sure to attend.
The event will take place via Zoom.
Meeting ID: 994 7248 4217 If you are unable to make either dates, then:
Learn more about the club on the about us page Visit the wiki to learn more about our projects Join the community discord, say hi, and ask any questions that you may have</description></item><item><title>Fall 2021 Callout</title><link>https://www.purduearc.com/post/f21-callout/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.purduearc.com/post/f21-callout/</guid><description>Following Purdue&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 protocol, we expect to have in-person callout events this semester. For students uncomfortable meeting in-person, we will host a live-stream session of the event.
Any student who plans on attending in-person is required to wear a mask.
The dates and times of these callout events are shown below:
August 31st
Time: 6:00-7:00 PM EST Location: ARMS B061 Live-stream link September 1st
Time: 6:00-7:00 PM EST Location: ARMS B061 Live-stream link Both callout events will contain the same information, so attending both is not required.</description></item><item><title>Robot Arm Project Fall 2021</title><link>https://www.purduearc.com/post/f21-robot-arm-announcement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.purduearc.com/post/f21-robot-arm-announcement/</guid><description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Raghava, the software lead, along with Sara, our hardware lead for the Robot Arm project at ARC.
If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re interested in being apart of the robot arm project! I&amp;rsquo;m excited to work with you guys and build an awesome robot arm.
Onboarding So, I&amp;rsquo;m a new project member, what should I do?
So, if you&amp;rsquo;re new to the project, we&amp;rsquo;ll try our best to get you up to speed ASAP on our project with our onboarding tools we built:</description></item><item><title>Fall 2021 Onboarding</title><link>https://www.purduearc.com/post/f21-onboarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.purduearc.com/post/f21-onboarding/</guid><description>Thanks to everyone who attended our callout events this semester. This post is meant to clear any confusion about next steps.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, ensure you have both joined the Discord and signed up through Boilerlink. These are essential for staying up-to-date with recent club events.
The following sections will outline next steps depending on your interests.
Joining an ongoing project Ongoing projects are ones that have been carried over from previous semesters.</description></item></channel></rss>